{
  "Deck 4": [
    {
      "STT": 1,
      "front": "Thanks",
      "back": "Cảm ơn"
    },
    {
      "STT": 2,
      "front": "Divide",
      "back": "Chia"
    },
    {
      "STT": 3,
      "front": "Preferences",
      "back": "Sở thích"
    }
  ],
  "Deck 3": [
    {
      "STT": 1,
      "front": "Please",
      "back": "Vui lòng"
    },
    {
      "STT": 2,
      "front": "Multiply",
      "back": "Nhân"
    },
    {
      "STT": 3,
      "front": "Settings",
      "back": "Cài đặt"
    },
    {
      "STT": 4,
      "front": "tuan",
      "back": "dep trai"
    },
    {
      "STT": 5,
      "front": "hehe",
      "back": "dep trai"
    }
  ],
  "Deck 2": [
    {
      "STT": 1,
      "front": "Goodbye",
      "back": "Tạm biệt"
    },
    {
      "STT": 2,
      "front": "Subtract",
      "back": "Trừ"
    },
    {
      "STT": 3,
      "front": "Options",
      "back": "Tùy chọn"
    },
    {
      "STT": 4,
      "front": "tuan",
      "back": "dep trai"
    },
    {
      "STT": 5,
      "front": "hehe",
      "back": "haha"
    }
  ],
  "Deck 1": [
    {
      "STT": 1,
      "front": "Hello",
      "back": "Xin chào"
    },
    {
      "STT": 2,
      "front": "Add",
      "back": "Cộng, thêm"
    },
    {
      "STT": 3,
      "front": "Setting",
      "back": "Cài đặt"
    },
    {
      "STT": 4,
      "front": "tu minh tuan",
      "back": "dep trai"
    }
  ]
}